Guide to the Bakery, Confectionery, and Tobacco Workers International Union, Local 3 Records and Photographs WAG 135
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Officers' Papers, 1946-1987; 30244
  - Sandroff Papers, unsorted, 1950-1959, 1960-1969; 30268 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Sandroff Papers, Class (School of Industrial Labor Relations at Cornell)-Handouts and Notes, 1967; 30267 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Benjamin v. Local 354 (Elmira, NY), Dec 1971; 30266 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Benjamin v. Local 252 (Calgary, Alberta), Dec 1971 - Jan 1972; 30265 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Brill et al v. Local 372B (Indianapolis, IN), Sep 1978; 30264 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Graeves v. Local 37 (Los Angeles, CA), Feb 1974; 30263 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-R. Hall (Local 163-Houston, TX) v. S. Pryor, Nov 1978; 30262 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Hernandez v. Local 163 (Houston, TX), Oct 1972; 30261 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Holmes Appeal Local 149 (Memphis, TN), May 1984 - Jun 1984; 30260 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-R. Horton Local 315 (San Diego, CA), Jan 1974; 30259 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Hummel v. Officers of Local 492 (Philadelphia, PA), Sep 1979; 30258 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Hummel v. Officers of Local 492-Supporting Material (Philadelphia, PA), Sep 1979; 30257 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Kelly v. Local 66 (Buena Park, CA), Jul 1972; 30256 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Judkin v. Local 372B (Indianapolis, IN), Nov 1971; 30255 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Local 81 Protest of Offices' Election (Traverse City, MI), Nov 1984; 30254 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Local 434 (Macon, GA), Mar 1977; 30253 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-McIntyre Appeal Local 50 (New York), Oct 1980; 30252 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Medina v. Local 163 (Houston, TX), Jul 1974; 30251 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-R. Miller & Election Committee Local 400 (Los Angeles, CA), 1974; 30250 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Nails v. Local 163 (Houston, TX), May 1973; 30249 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Weller v. Local 116 (Syracuse, NY), 1972; 30248 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Trustee Hearing Local 213 (Cincinnati, OH), Oct 1986; 30247 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Trusteeship Hearing Local 233 (Danville, VA), Jan 1987; 30246 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Lorber Papers, Hearings-Trusteeship Hearing Local 452 (Brooklyn, NY), Oct 1987; 30245 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Series III: Bargaining and Arbitration Records, 1954-1987; 30217
  This series contains Local 3 standard contracts, agreements and negotiation notes. Also included at the end of this series are four files of notes and contracts pertaining to Locals 51, 153, 579 and the Specialty Bakery Owners of America. Included in these files can be found the negotiation notes of Frank Dutto, Harry Lorber and Michael Sandroff. (Note: For the arbitration between Local 3 and particular shops, consult Series IV: Shop Files.)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, 1956-1959; 30243 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, Folder 1, 1960-1965; 30242 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, Folder 2, 1960-1965; 30241 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, 1965-1968; 30240 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, 1968-1971; 30239 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, 1971-1974; 30238 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, 1975-1981; 30237 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, 1980-1989; 30236 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1965; 30235 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1967; 30234 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1968; 30233 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1971; 30232 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1972-1973; 30231 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1974; 30230 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1975; 30229 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, Retail Stipulations-Signed Copies, 1975; 30228 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, Wage Comparisons, 1973-1977; 30227 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1978; 30226 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1981; 30225 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1982-1983; 30224 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1984; 30223 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, 1986-1987; 30222 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, Local 51, 1968-1971; 30221 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Contract Negotiations, Office Employees, Local 153, 1968-1975; 30220 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Standard Contracts and Agreements, Local 579, 1954; 30219 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Standard Contract Negotiations, Specialty Bakery Owners of America, 1968; 30218 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Series IV: Shop Files, 1964-1989; 29778
  All materials dealing with contract negotiation and disputes pertaining to a particular shop or company can be found in these files. Represented here are Local 3's bargaining sessions and agreements with small family-run bake shops, as well as protracted negotiations with corporate entities such as Drakes, Entenmann's and Ellio's Pizza House. In 1974 fierce negotiations took place between union and management at Ellio's -- a tri-lingual shop. Of particular interest are the leaflets in English, Greek, and Spanish that were generated during the conflict. Matzoh-Noodle Shops, Bagel Shops, and the New Jersey Division held separate collective bargaining sessions and files document these negotiations. In a sub-series called "Shops Closed" are the records that the union kept from 1964 - 1976 of shops that either went out of business or ended their union affiliation.
  - Shop Files, Route Ledger Code List, 1975; 30216 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Abraham Kosher Bread Shop, 1981-1982; 30215 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - American Bakeries Corporation, 1979-1981; 30214 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Anbar Bake Shop, Inc., 1982; 30213 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Arnold Bakers, Inc, 1972-1974; 30212 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Aster Nut Production, Inc., 1974; 30211 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Au Bon Pain Corp., 1983; 30210 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Augies Bakery Shop, 1983; 30209 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Au P'tit Pain, Inc., 1985; 30208 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Bagel Chips, Inc., 1985; 30207 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bagel Division, Collective Bargaining, 1972-1976; 30206 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Bagel Division, Collective Bargaining-Negotiation Notes (H. Lorber), 1974-1976; 30205 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Bagel Division, Collective Bargaining, 1977; 30204 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bagel Division, 1979-1983; 30203 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bagel Division, 1986; 30202 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Bagel Division, Clipping and Realia, 1970; 30201 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Barbara Bakery, Inc., 1985; 30200 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Barbero Bakery, Inc., 1980-1982; 30199 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Bellman's Bakery, 1976; 30198 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Bialy (Kuchen) Division, 1974-1986; 30197 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Bickford Commissary, 1968-1971; 30196 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Broadway Pastries, 1974-1982; 30195 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Cake Stylist, Inc., 1981-1985; 30194 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Cassone Bakery, Inc., 1977, 1982; 30193 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Certified Baking Co., 1985-1988; 30192 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - City Bakery, 1973-1982; 30191 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - City Bakery, 1983-1986; 30190 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Continental Seasonings, Inc., undated; 30189 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Continental Food Products, Inc., 1968, 1975-1982; 30188 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Corona Pastries, 1975; 30187 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Dainty Cookies, 1974; 30186 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Danilow Pastry Co. Inc., 1973-1983; 30185 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Daylight Bakery, 1986; 30184 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Delices La Cote Basque, Ltd., 1982-1983; 30183 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Delices La Cote Basque, Ltd., Negotiation Notes (H. Lorber), 1982; 30182 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Delmar Incorporated, 1976; 30181 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Des-Ches, Inc., 1986; 30180 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Dough Re Mi Bake Shop, 1982; 30179 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Drakes, 1968; 30178 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Drakes, 1970-1974; 30177 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Drakes, 1975-1976; 30176 (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Drakes, 1977-1978; 30175 (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Drakes, Negotiation Notes, 1977; 30174 (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Drakes, 1979; 30173 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Drakes, Negotiation Notes, 1979; 30172 (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Drakes, 1980-1981; 30171 (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Drakes, 1982; 30170 (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Drakes, 1983; 30169 (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Drakes, Jan 1984 - May 1984; 30168 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Drakes, Jun 1984 - Dec 1984; 30167 (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Drakes, Negotiation Notes, 1984-1985; 30166 (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Drakes, 1985-1986; 30165 (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Drakes, 1987; 30164 (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Dubin's Bakery Inc. (International Caribbean Delicasies, Inc.), 1982; 30162 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Dubrows Seventh, Inc., 1982; 30161 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Duvernoy Bakeries, 1964-1969; 30160 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dyckman Baking Corp., 1981-1983; 30159 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ebinger Baking Co., 1976, 1982; 30158 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Eclair Pastry, Inc., 1976; 30157 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Eclair Pastry, Inc., Office Worker, 1976, 1985; 30156 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Organizing Campaign, undated, 1974; 30155 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Organizing Campaign, Sep 1974 - Dec 1974; 30154 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, 1975-1976; 30153 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Contract (Annotated Draft and Final Version), 1975; 30152 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Lorber Negotiation Notes, 1974-1975; 30151 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, 1977-1978; 30150 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Lorber Negotiation Notes, 1977; 30149 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, 1979-1980; 30148 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Collective Bargaining Agreement, 1980; 30147 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, 1981-1988; 30146 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Lorber Negotiation Notes, 1986; 30145 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, 1988; 30144 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Ellio's Pizza House, Purex Industries Publication (Ellio's Parent Company), 1974, 1980; 30143 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Entenmann's, 1976; 30142 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Entenmann's, 1979-1980; 30141 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Entenmann's, Jan 1981 - Jun 1981; 30140 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Entenmann's, Jul 1981 - Dec 1981; 30139 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Entenmann's, 1982; 30138 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Entenmann's, 1983-1984; 30137 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Entenmann's, 1985; 30136 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Entenmann's, Jan 1986 - May 1986; 30135 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Entenmann's, 1987; 30134 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Entenmann's, Lorber's Note, 1986-1987; 30133 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Entenmann's, 1988-1989; 30132 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Entenmann's, Rentrite Havlage Corp., 1981-1985; 30131 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Entenmann's, Legal-Local 50 Health Benefits Fund v. Local 3, Jun 1982 - Jul 1982; 30130 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Entenmann's, Legal-Local 50 Health Benefits Fund v. Local 3, Jul 1982 - Aug 1982; 30129 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Entenmann's, Legal-Local 50 Health Benefits Fund v. Local 3, Aug 1982; 30128 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Entenmann's, Legal-Local 50 Health Benefits Fund v. Local 3, Mar 1983; 30127 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Excellent Bagels, Inc., 1986; 30126 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Family Bakers, Inc. (Master Bakers), 1971; 30125 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fifth Avenue Bake Shop, 1983; 30124 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1972-1975; 30123 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1980-1981; 30122 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1982; 30121 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1983; 30120 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1984; 30119 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1983-1987; 30118 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Fink Baking Corp., 1988-1989; 30117 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Five Corners Baking Co., 1985; 30116 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Flatland Bagel, 1975; 30115 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Food for Juniors, 1981-1983; 30114 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Freedman's Bakery, Inc., 1971; 30113 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Galaxy Bagels, Inc., 1979; 30112 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Gelbstein Baking Company, 1971-1980; 30111 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - General Spice, Inc., 1975-1976; 30110 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Gig Young Bakeries, 1975-1976; 30109 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Gnome Baking Company (Fink Subsidiary), 1976-1977; 30108 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Gnome Baking Company (Fink Subsidiary), Office Workers, 1970-1979; 30107 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Gnome Baking Company (Fink Subsidiary), 1979, 1981; 30106 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Gnome Baking Company (Fink Subsidiary), Office Workers, 1982, 1985; 30105 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Gold Medal Baking, Inc., 1986; 30104 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Goodman's (A. Goodman's & Sons, Inc.), 1970-1979; 30103 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Goodman's (A. Goodman's & Sons, Inc.), 1981; 30102 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Gotham Bagels, Inc., undated; 30101 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Grand Union Company, 1981-1983; 30100 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Guttenplans Bakery, 1971; 30099 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Gyro Restaurants, 1986; 30098 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - H & F Baking Co., Inc. (DBA-Parnes Bakery), 1982; 30097 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - H & F Parnes Bakery, 1983-1986; 30096 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - H & H Bagels, 1977; 30095 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - H & H Bagels, 1978; 30094 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - H & H Bagels, 1979-1981; 30093 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - H & H Bagels, Legal-H & H v. BCT, Local 3, 1978; 30092 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Harrison Baking Company, Inc., 1977-1979; 30091 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Harrison Baking Company, Inc., 1980-1981; 30090 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Harrsion Baking Company, Inc., 1982-1983; 30089 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Harrison Baking Company, Inc., 1984-1988; 30088 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - (Mrs.) Herbst Pastry & Strudels, Inc., 1982; 30087 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Hi Gluten Bakers, Inc., 1980; 30086 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Holes Unlimited, Inc., 1980; 30085 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Horn & Hardart Company, 1937; 30084 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Horn & Hardart Company, 1962-1963; 30083 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Horn and Hardart Company, 1968-1970; 30082 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Horowitz Bros. & Margareten, 1967; 30081 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Horowitz Bros. & Margareten, 1970-1981; 30080 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Horowitz Bros. & Margareten, 1979-1982; 30079 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Horowitz Bros. & Margareten, 1983-1985; 30078 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Hungarian Pastry Shop, 1972; 30077 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Hot Bagels & Donuts of Staten Island, Inc., 1975-1976; 30076 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Howard Johnson Commisary, 1970-1972; 30075 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., 1975-1976 Apr.; 30074 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., May 1976 - Dec 1976; 30073 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., Lorber Negotiation Notes, 1976; 30072 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., 1979; 30071 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., 1981-1982; 30070 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., 1985; 30069 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Industrial Devices, Inc., 1988; 30068 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Industrial Fresh Way, Inc., 1973; 30067 (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Interbaco Manhattan Corporation, 1974-1977; 30066 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Interboro Bakery Corporation, 1978; 30065 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Jumbo Bagels, 1983; 30064 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - K.P. Services, 1983-1986; 30063 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kartzman, Inc., 1982-1983; 30062 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Kohn's Bakery, Inc., 1972-1978; 30061 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Kuchen, 1977-1978; 30060 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - LaEsperanza Baking Company, Inc., 1978-1987; 30059 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Lambert's Bakery (Bergan Mall, Smithhaven Mall, Kings Mall, Willowbrook Mall), 1970-1975; 30058 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Lambert's Bakery (Bergan Mall, Smithhaven Mall, Kings Mall, Willowbrook Mall), 1976-1985; 30057 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Leonard's Baking Company, 1983; 30056 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Larsen Baking Co., 1981; 30055 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Les Delices Guy Pascal., Ltd., 1984-1985; 30054 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lessings, Inc., 1971-1979; 30053 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Lessings, Inc., 1970-1974; 30052 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Lessings, Inc., 1981-1985; 30051 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Liberty Bell Baking Company, 1987; 30050 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Linda Pita, 1989; 30049 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Linden's of Westchester, 1974-1982; 30048 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Linden's of Westchester, 1983-1986; 30047 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Linden Plaza Bagels, Inc., 1973; 30046 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Linwood Bakery, Inc., 1971-1982; 30045 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - M&B Bagels, Inc., 1983; 30044 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - M&R Baking Company, 1983; 30043 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Madison Baking Company, Inc. (Temtee Donuts Subsidiary), 1974; 30042 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Madnicks Bakery, 1987; 30041 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Mall Bakery, Inc., 1971; 30040 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1970; 30039 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1971-1973; 30038 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1976; 30037 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, Employees Pension Plan, 1977; 30036 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1978- 1980; 30035 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1981-1982; 30034 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, Negotiation Notes (Lorber; Schenkman), 1982; 30033 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1983; 30032 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - B. Manischewitz Company, 1984-1986; 30031 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - Marathon Enterprises, 1968-1975; 30030 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Marathon Enterprises, 1976; 30029 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Marathon Enterprises, 1981-1986; 30028 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Matzoh-Noodle Shop, Collective Bargaining, 1970-1979; 30027 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Miller Baking Company, 1982; 30026 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Miss Grimble, Inc., 1974; 30025 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Moka Pastry, Inc., 1983; 30024 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Montana Bakery, 1985; 30023 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Mrs. Maxwell's Bakeries, Ltd., 1983; 30022 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Mountain Shops, 1978-1982; 30021 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Muzenmaier Baking Company, 1978; 30020 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - New Colonial Bakery, 1981, 1987; 30019 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - New Jersey Division, 1971, 1973; 30018 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - New Jersey Division, 1977-1980; 30017 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - New Jersey Division, 1983; 30016 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Novel Cookie, 1970-1974; 30015 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Old Fashioned Kitchen, Inc., 1974; 30014 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Old Mill Enterprise, 1986; 30013 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Pampered Bagels, Inc., 1977; 30012 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Parnes Bakery, 1973; 30011 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Party Cake, 1983; 30010 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Passaic Baking Co., 1974; 30009 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Paterson Bagel Company, 1976, 1983; 30008 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Patisserie Dumas Co., Inc., 1982; 30007 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Patisserie Dumas Co., Inc., 1983; 30006 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Patisserie Dumas Co., Inc., 1984; 30005 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Patisserie Dumas Co., Inc., 1984; 30004 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Patisserie Dumas Co., Inc., 1987; 30003 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Pechter Baking Co., 1964; 30002 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Pechter Baking Co., 1979-1983; 30001 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Perth Amboy, 1980; 30000 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Pitta's Bakery Corp., 1974-1982; 29999 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Pride Baking Co., 1985; 29998 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Prudential Baking Co., 1987; 29997 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - R.K. Baking Corporation, 1975-1977; 29996 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - R.K. Baking Corporation, 1980-1981; 29995 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - R.P.M.I., Inc., 1979; 29994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Reisman Bros., 1981-1985; 29993 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Restaurant Associates, General, 1981-1987; 29992 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Restaurant Associates, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1973-1978; 29991 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Restaurant Associates, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1979-1984; 29990 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Restaurant Associates, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1985-1986; 29989 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Restaurant Associates, Metropolitan Museum of Art, 1987-1988; 29988 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Royale Bake Shop, 1973; 29987 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - S&S Cheesecake, Inc., 1975; 29986 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Saul & Stan, Ltd. (DBA Brooks Coffee Shop, Inc.), 1982; 29985 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Schrafft's Commissiary, 1968-1970; 29984 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Sheffs Baker Shop, 1982; 29983 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Silverock Baking Corp., 1981-1986; 29982 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Sinclair's Bobka Bakeries, 1981-1982; 29981 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - 63 Bake Shop Inc., 1981; 29980 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Spilke Bakery Incorporated, 1974-1975; 29979 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Strathmore Bagels, Inc., 1979; 29978 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - Aron Streit, Inc., 1967; 29977 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Aron Streit, Inc., 1970-1975; 29976 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - Aron Streit, Inc., 1976-1979; 29975 (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Aron Streit, Inc., 1982-1983; 29974 (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - Aron Streit, Inc., 1985; 29973 (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - Succes La Cote Basque Ltd., 1985; 29972 (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - Suzy Bake Shop, Inc., 1982; 29971 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - Table Talk Pies, Inc., 1975; 29970 (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Tremont Baking Company, 1982-1983; 29969 (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - Turnpike Bagels, Inc., 1976-1980; 29968 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Victory Baking Company, 1985; 29967 (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Vie de France, 1982; 29966 (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - Voila Bakery, 1980-1982; 29965 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - Voila Bakery, 1983-1984; 29964 (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - Voila Bakery, 1986; 29963 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Waldorf Bakers, 1984; 29962 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Watson Bagel Corp., 1981; 29961 (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Weisens Food, Inc., 1983; 29960 (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Well Bread Loaf Bakery, 1981; 29959 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - Wigler's Bakery, Inc., 1978-1981; 29958 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Wild Baking Company, 1973-1978; 29957 (Box 18, Folder 58)
  - William Greenberg Jr. Desserts Inc., 29956 (Box 18, Folder 59)
  - Wilton Caterers, 1972-1973; 29955 (Box 18, Folder 60)
  - Wold Class Kosher (DBA Gelstein's), 1986; 29954 (Box 18, Folder 61)
  - Wuest Health & Dietetic Foods Inc., 1972; 29953 (Box 18, Folder 62)
  - Your Neighborhood Baker Inc., Bankruptcy records, 1977; 29952 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Yoss Bros. Baking Corp., 1973; 29951 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Zaro Bake Shop Inc., 1980-1988; 29950 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Shops Closed, A&A Bakery, Inc., 1973; 29949 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Shops Closed, A.B.S. Bakeries, Inc., 1974; 29948 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Shops Closed, A&K Baking Corp., 1972-1973; 29947 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Shops Closed, Adrian Bake Shop, 1973-1974; 29946 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Shops Closed, Almo Bake Shop, 1964-1966; 29945 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Shops Closed, Alvinor Corp., 1964; 29944 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Shops Closed, Amsel Pastry, 1969; 29943 (Box 19, Folder 7a)